webmaster-tips.net 2017-12-01

# Privacy Policy

### Introduction.

We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel comfortable using our web site. This Privacy Policy deals with personally identifiable information (referred to as "Data" below) that may be collected by us on our site. 

This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control or persons that are not our employees, agents or within our control. Please take time to read our Terms of Use.  

###  1\. Collection of Data.

Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. 

Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. 

This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.  

###  2\. Use of Data.

We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.

###  3\. Cookies.

In compliance with the European Union legislation, we inform you that our website Webmaster-tips.net will store some information about your preferences how the website looks and operates on your own computer inside a tiny file called a 'cookie'. 

A cookie is a small piece of data that a website asks your browser to store on your computer or mobile device. The cookie allows the website to "remember" your actions or preferences over time. 

You can delete all cookies that are already on your computer and you can set most browsers to prevent them from being placed. If you do this, however, you may have to manually adjust some preferences every time you visit a site and some services and functionalities may not work. 

Most browsers support cookies, but users can set their browsers to decline them and can delete them whenever they like. A third-party website called [aboutcookies.org](http://aboutcookies.org/) has been setup to help you with instructions how you can do that on various browsers. 

We use cookies to: 

> \- identify you as a returning user and to count your visits in our traffic statistics analysis; 

> \- remember your custom display preferences; 

> \- suggest the last phones you've searched for in our Phone search field; 

> \- other usability features including tracking whether you've already given your consent to cookies 

Enabling cookies from Webmaster-tips.net is not strictly necessary for the website to work but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. 

The cookie-related information is not used to identify you personally and the pattern data is fully under our control. These cookies are not used for any purpose other than those described here. 

There may also be other types of cookies created after you've visited our website. 

We use Google Analytics, a popular web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google Analytics uses cookies to help us to analyse how users use the site. It counts the number of visitors and tells us things about their behaviour overall - such as the typical length of stay on the site or the average number of pages a user views. 

The information generated by the cookie about your use of our website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of our website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. 

Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google undertakes not to associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. 

###  4\. Advertisers

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) . 

### 5\. Children.

We do not allow persons who are ages thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact our webmaster.

###  6\. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information.

We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration by using your personal page configuration area. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting our webmaster. 

Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.  

###  7\. Changes to this Privacy Policy.

We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.

###  8\. No guarantees.

While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. 

As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.  

###  9\. Contact Information.

If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact website administrator .
